我懂了
I see.
好吧...
Well...
我要走了
I think I'll be going.
- Sheldon...  - 别说话
- Sheldon...  - No, no, no, no.
我们谈完了
We are done here.
你能不能打开门
Would you mind opening the door
然后非常生气地在我背后关上？
and then angrily slamming it behind me?
当然
Sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
注意摔狠点
And slam it hard,
因为我非常生气
because I am pretty steamed.
好吧 Leonard 别伤心
All right, Leonard, hang in there.
明天见
Talk to you tomorrow.
怎么了？ 他们才刚结婚
What happened? They just got married.
我不知道
I don't know.
乱七八糟的 他们在维加斯大吵了一架
It's a mess. They had a huge fight in Vegas.
你觉得他们会分手吗？
Think they'll break up?
不晓得 听着挺糟糕的
I don't know. Sounds pretty bad.
Penny一个人搬回她公寓了
Penny's back in her apartment all by herself.
是咩？
Really?
你想不想再听一个
Would you like to hear another reason
男人比女人好的原因？
why men are better than women?
当然 凑齐一百个吧
Sure, let's make it an even hundred.
你绝对不会吻我 然后让我说"我爱你"
You would never kiss me and make me say "I love you"
然后跟我分手
and then break up with me.
我确实不会
I wouldn't.
你知道为什么吗？
And you know why?
因为你是个男人
'Cause you're a man.
性别里的香槟酒
The champagne of genders.
我虽然是个男人
Well, I may be a man,
但我觉得这次是我把事情搞砸了
but I think I'm the one that screwed up on this one.
好吧 但你承认了 像个男人一样
Yeah, well, and you admit it, like a man.
女人们就只会说
All you hear women say is,
"我点个沙拉就好" 对不?
"I'll just have a salad." You know?
"我的润唇膏呢？"
"Where's my lip gloss?"
"我觉得这个元素应该叫镭"
"I think this element should be called radium."
最后一个是居里夫人
That last one was Madame Curie.
我猜出来了
I figured that out.
你知道吗？ 她算是名义上的男人
You know what? She was kind of an honorary man.
科学给了她男人的家伙
She had a penis made of science.
真不敢相信我新婚夜是跟你过的
Can't believe I'm spending my wedding night with you.
是吗？
Really?
这一直是我预料的结果
I never imagined it any other way.
我不知道
I don't know.
乱七八糟的 他们在维加斯大吵了一架
It's a mess. They had a huge fight in Vegas.
你觉得他们会分手吗？
Think they'll break up?
不晓得 听着挺糟糕的
I don't know. Sounds pretty bad.
Penny一个人搬回她公寓了
Penny's back in her apartment all by herself.
是咩？
Really?
你想不想再听一个
Would you like to hear another reason
男人比女人好的原因？
why men are better than women?
当然 凑齐一百个吧
Sure, let's make it an even hundred.
你绝对不会吻我 然后让我说"我爱你"
You would never kiss me and make me say "I love you"
然后跟我分手
and then break up with me.
我确实不会
I wouldn't.
你知道为什么吗？
And you know why?
因为你是个男人
'Cause you're a man.
性别里的香槟酒
The champagne of genders.
我虽然是个男人
Well, I may be a man,
但我觉得这次是我把事情搞砸了
but I think I'm the one that screwed up on this one.
好吧 但你承认了 像个男人一样
Yeah, well, and you admit it, like a man.
女人们就只会说
All you hear women say is,
"我点个沙拉就好" 对不?
"I'll just have a salad." You know?
"我的润唇膏呢？"
"Where's my lip gloss?"
"我觉得这个元素应该叫镭"
"I think this element should be called radium."
最后一个是居里夫人
That last one was Madame Curie.
我猜出来了
I figured that out.
你知道吗？ 她算是名义上的男人
You know what? She was kind of an honorary man.
科学给了她男人的家伙
She had a penis made of science.
真不敢相信我新婚夜是跟你过的
Can't believe I'm spending my wedding night with you.
是吗？
Really?
这一直是我预料的结果
I never imagined it any other way.